[
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for stone:",
       "choices" : ["rock","grass", "branch","flower"],
       "correctanswer": 0
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for correspondence:",
       "choices" : ["letters or emails","legle custody", "legal correction","redio transmissions"],
       "correctanswer": 0
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for concentration:",
       "choices" : ["conservation","permission", "ambition","attention"],
       "correctanswer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for fail:",
       "choices" : ["not try","not succeed", "drop","see"],
       "correctanswer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for harbor:",
       "choices" : ["captain","path", "corner","port"],
       "correctanswer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for guideline:",
         "choices" : ["sponsor","finish line", "rule","guide dog"],
         "correctanswer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for corrupt:",
       "choices" : ["easygoing","reputable", "secreativ","dishonest"],
       "correctanswer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Choose the best synonym for stream:",
       "choices" : ["small river","small airplan", "machine","small hill"],
       "correctanswer": 0
   },
   {
       "question":" Choose the best synonym for exist:",
       "choices" : ["assert","live", "perceive","insist"],
       "correctanswer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":" Choose the best synonym for graduate:",
       "choices" : ["move slowly","pass a test", "earn a diploma","complete a grade"],
       "correctanswer": 1
   }
]